Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes
  - Auden, W. H.: Will (3), undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Auden, W. H.: Will (4), undated (Box 3.1, Folder 6)
  - Auden, W. H.: Will (5), undated (Box 3.1, Folder 7)
  - Aueling, Stephen, undated (Box 4, Folder 1a)
  - Austen, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 1b)
  - [Austen-Leigh Papers: see Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers, Boxes 163-167.5.B and Legal & Oversize], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_f55446ab970fe9d565df60f4ad3fb1d5)
  - Austin, Alfred (1835-1913), undated (Box 4, Folder 1c)
  - Austin, Jane (Goodwin) (1831-1894), undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Austin, Mary (Hunter) (1868-1934), undated (Box 4, Folder 1e)
  - Austin, Roland, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Avebury, John Lubbock, Baron (1834-1913), undated (Box 4, Folder 1g)
  - Ayden, Erje: Correspondence, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ayden, Erje: Ms. The Crazy Green of Second Avenue, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ayden, Erje: Ms. The Legend of Erje Ayden [pp. 1-109], undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ayden, Erje: Ms. The Legend of Erje Ayden [pp. 110-233], undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ayden, Erje: Ms. The Summer Frank O'Hara Died (1), undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ayden, Erje: Ms. The Summer Frank O'Hara Died (2), undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ayden, Erje: Willem, the King of Hearts, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Ayer, James, undated (Box 4, Folder 9a)
  - Ayers, Ruby D., undated (Box 4, Folder 9b)
  - Aylmer, undated (Box 4, Folder 10a)
  - Aytoun, William Edmondstoune (1813-1865), undated (Box 4, Folder 10b)
  - Azimullah, undated (Box 4, Folder 10c)
  - Babbage, Charles (1792-1871), undated (Box 5, Folder 1a)
  - Baccante, Leonora, undated (Box 5, Folder 1b)
  - Bacheller, Irving, undated (Box 5, Folder 1c)
  - Bacon, Josephine Daskam, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bacon, Leonard W. (1830-1907), undated (Box 5, Folder 1e)
  - Badger, Stephen (1726-1803), undated (Box 5, Folder 2a)
  - Bage, Robert (1728-1801), undated (Box 5, Folder 2b)
  - Bagnold, Enid, undated (Box 5, Folder 2c)
  - Bailey, Philip James (1816-1902), undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Baillie, Joanna (1762-1851): 42 letters, 5 envelopes, 2 MATs, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - [Baird, Charles Washington: see Boxes 6-10], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_24e4e7efac91389a9dd6d4cf73df2b0e)
  - [Bakeless, John: see Box 12], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_62107614bfc9f314f2232292ccf9defc)
  - Baker, Abijah Richardson (1805-1876), undated (Box 5, Folder 4a)
  - Baker, George Fales (ca. 1872-1905), undated (Box 5, Folder 4b)
  - Baker, Harriet Newell Woods (1815-1893), undated (Box 5, Folder 4c)
  - Baker, Ray Stannard, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Baker, Samuel White, Sir (1821-1893), undated (Box 5, Folder 4e)
  - Balchin, Nigel (1908- ): 23 letters, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Baldwin, Stanley, 1st Earl (1867-1947), undated (Box 5, Folder 6a)
  - Balfour, Arthur James, 1st Earl (1848-1930), undated (Box 5, Folder 6b)
  - Balfour, Graham W., undated (Box 5, Folder 6c)
  - Ballantine, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 7a)
  - Ballantyne, James (1772-1833), undated (Box 5, Folder 7b)
  - Ballantyne, John (1774-1821), undated (Box 5, Folder 7c)
  - Ballantyne, Robert Michael (1825-1894), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Ballou, Jenny, undated (Box 5, Folder 7e)
  - Bancroft, Frederick W., undated (Box 5, Folder 8a)
  - Bancroft, George (1800-1891), undated (Box 5, Folder 8b)
  - Bangs, John Kendrick (1862-1922), undated (Box 5, Folder 8c)
  - Banim, John (1798-1842), undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Banks, George Linnaeus (1821-1881), undated (Box 5, Folder 9a)
  - Banks, Isabelle Varley (1821-1897), undated (Box 5, Folder 9b)
  - Banks, Joseph, Sir (1743-1820), undated (Box 5, Folder 9c)
  - Barbauld, Anna Letitia (Mrs.) (1743-1825), undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Barclay, Florence Louisa (1862-1921), undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Barham, Richard (Harris) (1788-1845), undated (Box 5, Folder 12a)
  - Barham, Richard Harris Dalton (1815-1886?), undated (Box 5, Folder 12b)
  - Baring, Maurice (1870-1905), undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Baring-Gould, Sabine (1834-1924), undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Barker, Charles, undated (Box 5, Folder 15a)
  - Barnard, Edward (1717-1781), undated (Box 5, Folder 15b)
  - Barnard, F. C., undated (Box 5, Folder 15c)
  - Barnard, Frederick (1846-1896), undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Barnette, Henlee H., undated (Box 5, Folder 15e)
  - Barr, Amelia Edith (1831-1919), undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Barr, Robert (1850-1912), undated (Box 5, Folder 17a)
  - Barr, William (ca. 1825), undated (Box 5, Folder 17b)
  - Barrett, Mary, undated (Box 5, Folder 17c)
  - [Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew) (1860-1937): see Box 11], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_16c721bc20368d9883bd8e365c91f601)
  - Barrow, Fanny, undated (Box 5, Folder 18a)
  - Barrus, Clara, undated (Box 5, Folder 18b)
  - Bartlett, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 18c)
  - Barton, Bernard (1784-1849), undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Barton, Margaret: MS. David Garrick, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Baruch, Bernard, undated (Box 5, Folder 20a)
  - Bate, Samuel Stringer, undated (Box 5, Folder 20b)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Letterbook, v.1, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.2, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.3, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.4, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Huguenot Emigration: Letterbook, v.5, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.6, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.7, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.8, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Huguenot Emigration: Letterbook, v.9, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.10: 1 [pp. 2-168], undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.10: 2, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.10: 3, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.11: 1: letters [dated], undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Letterbook, v.11: 2, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.1, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.2, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.3, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.4, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.5-6, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.7, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.8, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.9, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): History of the Huguenot Emigration to America: Notebooks, v.10, Supplement, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Notebooks, A-C, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Notebooks, D-H, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Baird, Charles Washington (1828-1887): Notebooks, I-M, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew) (1860-1937): to E.V. [Lucas?], 1923-1934, NY (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew) (1860-1937), 1892-1935; undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew) (1860-1937): MSS. 1. Captain Hook at Eton; 2. "This little book was printed"; [see also Bound Volumes], undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew) (1860-1937): MS. The Admiral Crichton, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Barrie, J. M. (James Matthew) (1860-1937): Preface to Peter Pan: Labels, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bakeless, John Edwin (1894-1978): Lewis and Clark Expedition [pp. 1-99], undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bakeless, John Edwin (1894-1978): Lewis and Clark Expedition [pp. 100-199], undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bakeless, John Edwin (1894-1978): Lewis and Clark Expedition [pp. 200-299], undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Bakeless, John Edwin (1894-1978): Lewis and Clark Expedition [pp. 300-399], undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bakeless, John Edwin (1894-1978): Lewis and Clark Expedition [pp. 400-499], undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bakeless, John Edwin (1894-1978): Lewis and Clark Expedition [pp. 500-599], undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bakeless, John Edwin (1894-1978): Lewis and Clark Expedition [pp. 600-690], undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - [Barry, Charles: see Bryson, Charles, Box 22], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_5ff8c6a60c559c3082b1d05da385eb72)
  - Bates, Herbert Ernest, undated (Box 13, Folder 1a)
  - Bates, Katherine Lee (1859-1929), undated (Box 13, Folder 1b)
  - Baudelaire, Charles: Les Epares, 1934: 2 Etchings by Henri Le Riche (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Baum, Vicki, undated (Box 13, Folder 3a)
  - Bax, Clifford, undated (Box 13, Folder 3b)
  - Bayard, William, undated (Box 13, Folder 3c)
  - Baylis, Lilian Mary (1874-1937), undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Bayly, Ada Ellen (1857-1903), undated (Box 13, Folder 4a)
  - Bayly, Thomas Haynes (1797-1839), undated (Box 13, Folder 4b)
  - Beach, Rex, undated (Box 13, Folder 5a)
  - Beach, Sylvia, undated (Box 13, Folder 5b)
  - Beaconsfield, Benjamin Disraeli, 1st Earl of (1804-1887), undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Beard, Charles Austin (1874-1948), undated (Box 13, Folder 7a)
  - Beard, Daniel Carter (1850-1941), undated (Box 13, Folder 7b)
  - Beardsley, Aubrey (1877-1898), undated (Box 13, Folder 7c)
  - Beattie, James (1734-1803), undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Beauclerk, Diane, Lady (1734-1808), undated (Box 13, Folder 7e)
  - Beaumont, H., undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Beckford, William (1760-1804), undated (Box 13, Folder 8a)
  - [Bede, Cuthbert: see Bradley, Edward, Box 21], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_47786b9c9b11c0c2024c434bc5d3e98c)
  - Beebe, Charles William, undated (Box 13, Folder 8b)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward, undated (Box 13, Folder 8c)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward Eunice, Mrs., undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Beeding, Francis (1898-1951) (pseud. of Hilary Aidan St. George Saunders), undated (Box 13, Folder 8e)
  - Beer, Max (1864- ), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956): Correspondence, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956): MS. The Happy Hypocrite: adaptation by Ghedini with M.B. notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - [Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956)]: Greene, Stephen: The Seventh Scribe [master's thesis], undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - [Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956)]: [Knight, Arthur: The Hands Marked for Death. TV adaption], undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956): [Riewald, J. G.: Sir Max Beerbohm: Man and Writer. folders 1-2], undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956): [Riewald, J. G.: Sir Max Beerbohm: Man and Writer. folder 3: pp. 98-288], undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956): [Riewald, J. G.: Sir Max Beerbohm: Man and Writer. folder 4: Bibliography, pp. 289-401], undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956): [Riewald, J. G.: Sir Max Beerbohm: Man and Writer. folder 4B: pp. 289-401], undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Beerbohm, Max, Sir (1872-1956): "Aubrey Beardsley" from The Idler: printed material, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Beever, Susanna (d. 1893), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 1a)
  - Begbie, Harold, undated (Box 13.5, Folder 1b)
  - Beith, Janet, undated (Box 13.5, Folder 1c)
  - Beith, John Hay, undated (Box 13.5, Folder 1)
  - Beke, Charles Telstone, undated (Box 13.5, Folder 1e)
  - Belasco, David: The Return of Peter Grimm, undated (Box 13.5, Folder 2)
  - Bell, Eric Temple (John Taine, pseud.), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 3a)
  - Bell, Isaac Lothian, Sir (1816-1904), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 3b)
  - Bell, John Jay (1871-1934), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 3c)
  - Bell, Julian (1908-1937), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 3)
  - Bell, Lillian Lida (Mrs. A. H. Boque) (1867-1929), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 3e)
  - Bell, MacKenzie (1856-1930), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 4)
  - Bellamy, Edward (1850-1898), undated (Box 13.5, Folder 5)
  - Belloc, Hilaire (1870-1953): 20 pieces, 1909-1914 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Belloc, Hilaire (1870-1953): 21 pieces, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Belloc, Hilaire (1870-1953): 19 pieces, 1916-1917 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Belloc, Hilaire (1870-1953): 14 letters, 4 envelopes, 1920-1937 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Belloc, Hilaire (1870-1953): An Heroic Poem in Praise of Wine, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Belloc, Hilaire (1870-1953): 1 P.C. about Belloc, undated (Box 14, Folder 5a)
  - Benchley, Robert Charles (1889-1945), undated (Box 14, Folder 6a)
  - Benefield, Barry, undated (Box 14, Folder 6b)
  - Benet, Stephen Vincent, undated (Box 14, Folder 6c)
  - Benet, Stephen Vincent: Notebooks (2), undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Benet, William Rose, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Benger, Elizabeth Ogilvy, undated (Box 14, Folder 8a)
  - Benjamin, Park, undated (Box 14, Folder 8b)
  - Benjamin, S. G. W., undated (Box 14, Folder 8c)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Correspondence, 1899-1911 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Correspondence, 1912-1920 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Correspondence, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Correspondence, 1924-1931; undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Autobiography [undated]; Poem (1907), undated; 1907 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): MS. and TS. The Alarm (an unpublished play); TS. A Farce in One Act; The Snake Charmer, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Essays [undated; 1924-1929] (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Essays (May 1929-1930) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Clips, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Bennett, Arnold (1867-1931): Miscellany, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Benson, ___ [not E. F. or A. C.][to Benson], undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Benson, Arthur Christopher (1862-1925): 30 letters, 1 pc, 1 mat, 1 envelope, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1893-1895] (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1896] (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1897] (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1898] (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1900-1902] (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1903] (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1904] (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1905] (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1906] (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1907] (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1908-1911] (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1912] (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1913-1914] (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1915-1917] (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Benson, E. F. (Edward Frederic) (1867-1940): [1918-1938], 1918-1936 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Benson, Stella, undated (Box 16.5, Folder 1)
  - Benson, Stella: Pictorial. The Little World [removed from this title. Book does not indicate illustration.], undated (Box 16.5, Folder 2)
  - Bentley, Richard, undated (Box 16.5, Folder 3a)
  - Benton, Joel, undated (Box 16.5, Folder 3b)
  - Beresford, John Davys (1873-1947), undated (Box 16.5, Folder 4a)
  - Beresford-Hope, Alexander James Beresford (1820-1887), undated (Box 16.5, Folder 4b)
  - Berge´, Carol (Peppis), undated (Box 16.5, Folder 5)
  - Berger, Francesco, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Berger, Thomas, undated (Box 17, Folder 2a)
  - Berkeley, George Charles Grantley Fitzhardinge (1800-1881), undated (Box 17, Folder 2b)
  - Bernard, William Bayle (1807-1875), undated (Box 17, Folder 2c)
  - Bernhardt, Sarah (1844-1923), undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Berkson, Bill [for Tom Clark]: 12pp TS. (original, unsigned); 24pp. TS. (carbons), 11pp TS. (original), 8 miscellaneous, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Berrigan, Ted: MS. Many Happy Returns; TS. 24pp. with corrections, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Berrigan, Ted: MS. Tambourine; 18pp. TS. with corrections; 22pp. printed with corrections, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Berryman, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Besant, Annie: 2 letters [see also Elizabeth Robins Papers], undated (Box 17, Folder 7a)
  - Besant, Mary, undated (Box 17, Folder 7b)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): 40 letters, mostly to Colles, some to William Dickens, 1871-1885 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): 32 letters, mostly to Colles, 1886-1887 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): 21 letters, 1888 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): 33 letters, 1889 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): 23 letters, 1890 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): 42 letters, 1891 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): 29 letters, 1892 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1893 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1894 (Box 18.5, Folder 1)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1895 (Box 18.5, Folder 2)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1896 (Box 18.5, Folder 3)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1897 (Box 18.5, Folder 4)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1898 (Box 18.5, Folder 5)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1899 (Box 18.5, Folder 6)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), 1900-1901 (Box 18.5, Folder 7)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901), undated (Box 18.5, Folder 8)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): MSS., undated (Box 18.5, Folder 9)
  - Besant, Walter, Sir (1836-1901): Pictorial, undated (Box 18.5, Folder 10)
  - Beste, John Richard, undated (Box 19, Folder 1a)
  - Betjeman, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 1b)
  - Beveridge, Albert Jeremiah (1862-1927), undated (Box 19, Folder 1c)
  - Bierce, Ambrose (1842-1914), undated (Box 19, Folder 2a)
  - Bigelow, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 2b)
  - [Billings, Josh: see Shaw, Henry Wheeler, Box 157], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_9064041b2d496cc761f1278098fd4a16)
  - Bindloss, Harold, undated (Box 19, Folder 3a)
  - Binyon, Lawrence (1869-1943), undated (Box 19, Folder 3b)
  - Birbeck, George (1776-1841), undated (Box 19, Folder 4a)
  - Birney, Hoffman, undated (Box 19, Folder 4b)
  - Birrell, Augustine (1850-1933), undated (Box 19, Folder 4c)
  - Bishop, Henry Healsall, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Bishop, Henry Rowley (1786-1855), undated (Box 19, Folder 6a)
  - Bishop, Morris, undated (Box 19, Folder 6b)
  - Bispham, David Scull (1857-1921), undated (Box 19, Folder 6c)
  - Black, Robert (1829-1915): 14 letters, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Black, William (1841-1898): 54 letters, 1 MS. (5pp.); 1 photograph, 1865-1898; undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. At the Well [2pp. TSS.], undated (Box 19, Folder 9a)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. Here They Go [2pp. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9b)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. It Might as Well Be Spring [1p. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9c)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. On the Rocks [2pp. TSS. - to Clayton Eshleman], undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. 1962: Lent Begins with Difficulty [1p. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9e)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. [no title][1p. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. The Reality Invokes [1p. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9g)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. Sensemaya´ [12pp. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9h)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. Tequila [4pp. TSS]: P.B. and C. Eshleman, undated (Box 19, Folder 9i)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. We Live Regular... [2pp. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9j)
  - Blackburn, Paul: MS. What Elsie is New [2pp. TS.(c)], undated (Box 19, Folder 9k)
  - Blackie, John Stuart (1809-1895): 3 letters, undated (Box 19, Folder 10a)
  - Blackwood, Algernon (1869-1951):, 1908-1948; undated (Box 19, Folder 10b)
  - Blackwood, William (1776-1834), undated (Box 19, Folder 10c)
  - Blackwood, William (ca. 1878), undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Blades, William (1824-1890), undated (Box 19, Folder 10e)
  - Blaine, James G. (1830-1893), undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Blair, Emily (1877- ), undated (Box 19, Folder 10g)
  - Blair, Hugh (1718-1800), undated (Box 19, Folder 10h)
  - Blakemore, Richard Doddridge (1825-1900):, 1860-1881 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Blakemore, Richard Doddridge (1825-1900): [see also Oversize "B" letter, March 6, 1890, "My dear cousin..."], 1882-1890 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Blakemore Family: Richard Doddridge, Mrs. Lucy and Eva, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Blakewell, H., undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Blakewell, Richard S., undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Blakey, Robert (1795-1878), undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Blanchard, Samuel L. (1804-1845), undated (Box 19, Folder 17a)
  - Blasco-Ibanez, Vincente (1867-1928), undated (Box 19, Folder 17b)
  - Blessington, Marguerite (Power) Countess (1789-1849): [see also Oversize], 1825-1846; undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Blind, Karl (1826-1907), undated (Box 19, Folder 19a)
  - Bliss, Arthur, Sir (1891- ), undated (Box 19, Folder 19b)
  - Bliss, Geoffrey, undated (Box 19, Folder 19c)
  - Blone¨t, Paul (1848-1903) (Max O'Rell, pseud.), undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Blunden, Edmund Charles (1896-1974): 21 letters, 9 pc [1921-1960] (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Blunt, Wifred Scawen, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1a)
  - Boardman, Joseph, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1b)
  - Boardman, William J., undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1c)
  - Bobbe, Dorothie (DeBear), undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1)
  - Bogan, Louise, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1e)
  - Bogg, Marie, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1)
  - Bojer, Johan, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1g)
  - Bok, Edward William, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1h)
  - Boker, George Henry, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 1i)
  - Bonaparte Family: Napoleon I; Napoleon III, 1 envelope; Bonaparte, Jerome, 1 letter; Bonaparte, Joseph, 1 letter; Bonaparte, Lucien; Walewski, Alexander, 1 letter, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 2)
  - Bone, James, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3a)
  - Bone, Muirhead, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3b)
  - Bonnaire, H., undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3c)
  - Bonsal, Stephen (1865-1951), undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3)
  - Bonsels, Waldemar (1880 or 81-1952), undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3e)
  - Boone, Daniel, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3)
  - Boothby, Brooke, Sir (1743-1824), undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3g)
  - Boothby, Guy Newell (1867-1905), undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3h)
  - Borleau, Ethel Mary (1882-1942), undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3i)
  - Boroff, David, undated (Box 19.5, Folder 3j)